A Brush with Love is a romance, tv movie film directed by Peter DeLuise.
As she considers giving up on her artistic dreams, Jamie paints a vision board that brings her success
and love—only to discover that the mystery man in her painting isn't who she thinks.
Jamie, played by Arielle Kebbel.
Max, played by Nick Bateman.
Reporter, played by Arran Henn.
Ava Hughes, played by Hilary Jardine.
Real Estate Agent, played by James Rha.
Michael Herman, played by Matthew James Dowden.
De De Pyaar De 2 (transl.
'Give me love 2') is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language romantic comedy film directed by Anshul Sharma,
written by Luv Ranjan and Tarun Jain and produced by T-Series Films and Luv Films.
It is a sequel to De De Pyaar De (2019).
The film stars Ajay Devgn, R.
Madhavan and Rakul Preet Singh.
The film was announced in March 2024.
Principal photography commenced in June 2024, held in Punjab and London.
The film was theatrically released worldwide on 14 November 2025.
It received mixed reviews from critics and
underperformed at the box office, grossing est.
₹ 105 crore worldwide.
The film explores themes of artist, painter,
romance, painter as artist, hallmark.
The tone is emotional.